directagents.com 2014-11-07

# Privacy Policy | DirectAgents

Direct Agents, Inc., is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our websites. The following document outlines the privacy procedures and guidelines for our websites – www.directagents.com, www.da-tracking.com, and any other websites that we may launch in connection with our business. This policy was last updated January 19th, 2011.

**The Information We Collect**  
We automatically collect data related to your site visit, including IP address, referring URL, and time and date of visit. This information is collected for internal research purposes only and to identify and address any technical issues. In addition, you may voluntarily submit additional personally identifiable information, such as name, e-mail address, phone number, and physical address, in order to inquire about our company’s services or products. Direct Agents will store this information, and may use it to track your site visit.

**How We Use the Information**  
Direct Agents will use your personal information to conduct follow-up communication efforts with you, including email newsletters. In addition, Direct Agents may use your information to inform you of additional services and products from our clients and partners.

**No Information Collected from Minors**  
MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 18 SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO Direct Agents. If Direct Agents is notified it has any information about a minor under the age of 18, that information will be promptly deleted from our active database.

**Notice About Cookies**  
A “Cookie” is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows Direct Agents to identify your IP address with corresponding information in Direct Agents’ database. Cookies eliminate the need to re-enter information on a particular site, every time you visit that site. Cookies do not identify you personally, but can be used to identify your computer. Many website operators use this technology to better serve the visitors to their sites. Most browsers are set to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse them. You may read more about cookies at [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

**Site Security**  
Direct Agents and its affiliated websites are hosted securely in order to protect your privacy and personal information. We follow industry best practices to ensure the integrity of your data.

**Foreign Use of the Website**  
Foreign Domiciled users accessing this Website, acknowledge and consent that personal information provided to Direct Agents is collected and stored in the United States. You therefore consent to the transfer of such information out of your country of domicile, to the United States.

**US-EU Safe Harbor Compliance**  
Direct Agents complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Direct Agents has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view the company’s certification, please email us at [privacy@directagents.com](mailto:privacy@directagents.com) or please visit the Safe Harbor website at [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@directagents.com](mailto:privacy@directagents.com) or by phone at +1-212-925-6558 or by postal mail at the following address:

Direct Agents, Inc.  
740 Broadway, Suite 701  
New York, NY 10003

New Blog Post

Contact Us

  * 

Prospect Email resulting in tens of thousands of leads per month

  * 

Elevated organic traffic & 1st page results on high volume keywords

## New Blog Post

Meet Direct Agents at ad:tech New York

## Contact Us

For Best Practices in Digital Marketing
